Guide to the Molka Reich papers, 1904-1986
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 6: Scrapbooks, 1920s-1950s
  - Marionettes scrapbook, 1930s-1950s (Box 7, Folder 15)
    1 of 2. Contains primarily magazine and newspaper articles featuring marionettes. There is also a certificate for Mrs. Howard Fitch for completing the Cultural Olympics in Woodstown, New Jersey (May 5, 1938). Clippings and certificate are attached to scrapbook paper.
  - Marionettes scrapbook, 1930s-1950s (Box 7, Folder 16)
    2 of 2. Contains loose newspaper and magazine clippings featuring articles on marionettes.
  - Loose materials, circa 1938-1941 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Includes newsclippings, newsclippings attached to paper, a program, and marionette patterns.
  - Loose scrapbook materials, 1930s (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Includes programs for the West Florida Music and Arts Festival, International Society for Contemporary Music (1931), newspaper and magazine clippings featuring marionettes.
  - Marionettes by children loose scrapbook pages, circa 1930s (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Newspaper articles from the Monitor titled "Marionettes by Children" that illustrate how one can make their own marionette.
  - Miami scrapbook, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Oversize. Molka Reich scrapbook featuring newspaper clippings and programs from Miami Federal Theatre and non Federal Theatre productions. Pages have been separated.
  - Starlight Theater scrapbook, circa 1955 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Oversize. Scrapbook pages separated, featuring programs and newspaper clipping from productions performed at Starlight Theater in Pawling, New York.